Jarek Roszkowski

social media monitoring now!

Summary

20 years of experience in new & traditional media. Share in the success of businesses (media house Starlink, advertising network Ad-Vice, social media monitoring tool Brand24). Wide range of management experiences. The emphasis on analysis and strategy. Social media marketing enthusiast

Experience

Head of Analysis Department (social media monitoring company), Member of the Supervisory Board at Brand24

sierpień 2011 - Present

Development of analysis department

Visiting lecturer at Francuski Instytut Zarządzania wrzesień 2006 - Present

I teach media planning and social media marketing in the Executive MBA program.

Member of the Board, CMO (advertising network)

styczeń 2010 - luty 2012 (2 lata 2 mies.)

Creating new business strategy

Implementation of the strategy in the area of marketing and technology

Development and promotion of new products (such as Digital Young)

Promotional activities in the B2B channel - mainly internet marketing (Google, social media marketing)

Cooperation with publishers to promote websites on the B2B market (including group Demotywatory.pl)

Member of the Board in two companies: IMP (interactive agency) and Webtel (technology company) at Internet Group

marzec 2008 - grudzień 2009 (1 rok 10 mies.)

Restructuring of companies - to develop and implement a new structure within interactive agency IMP

Cooperation with companies from Internet Group (synergy at the operational level and product)

Supervision of the introduction of technological innovations

Strategy support for the sale of corporate offer at Internet Group SA

Finance supervision & budget planning

CEO (media broker of regional press)

marzec 2007 - wrzesień 2007 (7 mies.)

Modification of the current, short-term sales strategy

The development of new market strategy

The reorganization of resources and rules of cooperation with the publishers - to increase the efficiency of the sales department

Relationship Management's shareholders in the event of any change in their business strategy to the company

Negotiating with media houses

Introduction of new advertising product

Member of the Board, CMO (media house)

wrzesień 2001 - luty 2007 (5 lat 6 mies.)

Development and implementation of marketing strategy - to build awareness of the new-to-themarket company

The development of competence in the field of media planning

The development and introduction of new products - the first system on the market estimation of advertising budgets (estimates of net advertising market - Starlink report), strategic media planning system

Management of selected Clients' teams

Preparing the budget, financial oversight of the company

Education

Universite Lyon II

Economie de la production, 1994 - 1995

University of Gdansk

Master's degree, Marketing, 1990 - 1995

Jarek Roszkowski

social media monitoring now!



Contact Jarek on LinkedIn